Timing and Subtitles brought to you by I'm Busy Getting Stronger Team @ Viki
People ask me, "Why do you weightlift?"
When I was ten, I followed my father when he went to the weightlifting room.
I bizarrely liked the metallic smell of barbells that I smelled for the first time.
I thought to myself then, I would do weightlifting too.
Weightlifter Kim Bok Joo from Haneul Sports University is challenging the Clean &amp; Jerk 115 kg for the third time.
Haneul Sports University
I became a weight lifter at such a young age, and
I grew up together with weightlifting.
I have lifted the barbells and thrown them several thousand times.
I have scraped out calluses on my hands hundreds of times,
and I have poured out thousands of liters of sweat and tears
And now... I am almost on stage!
The third attempt of Kim Bok Joo from Haneul Sports University.
That's what I'm saying.
I told you.
- Here's the marinated chicken.  - Look!
Aigoo, don't mind me but enjoy your chicken.
Ah, what the heck?
Gold medal! She got gold!
- Gold medal! Gold medal! - She got the gold medal!
She's my daughter! My daughter!
- She is my niece!!  - My daughter!
The 96th National Weightlifting Competition Weight Lifting Stadium
Thank you! Thank you!
I enjoyed your performance. Let's see at Taerung Training Village (Korea National Training Center)
You are my role model. I'll work hard, Sunbae.
- Congrats! - Thank you!
I am a twenty-one year, in my blossoming year.
The Weightlifter Kim Bok Joo.
This is from Olympia Swimming Pool, where the 35th Presidential Cup National Swimming Competition is held.
Right now, Men's Group B is swimming the 200 meter freestyle preliminary.
Take your mark!
Right now, in lane 5...
Swimmer Jeong Joon Hyeong from Haneul Sports University
is showing us a tremendous speed. What kind of swimmer is he?
Yes, that swimmer has a good record during practices, and he is a rising star.
In a previous competition, he was unfortunately disqualified due to an early start.
Right now, the first place at the Group B preliminary is Swimmer Jeong Joon Hyeong.
When I look at the record,
he is 0.15 second faster than Swimmer Choi Tae Woon in Group A who holds the Korea record.
Yes!
Episode 1When you don't like food, you can give it to dog but when you don't like a person...
One! One! Two!
One! Two! Three! Four!
Hwaiting!
Weightlifting Team! Hwaiting!
Team! Fighting!
Team!Fighting!&lt;
Look! Look!
Lift! Good!
Watch her.
Hey, Bok Joo. Just like that! Okay.
You should endure it. Lift your gaze.
That's right. You have to lift it straight up!
Your back leg is shaking.
Do you know that you're losing your endurance?
Do the strength work later.
You were zoning out so you didn't do strength work earnestly.
Alright, let's stop the morning training here.
Let's gather. Yes!
Gather here!
You worked hard. Let me request one thing as your professor-in-charge.
The end is just as important as the start.
When I was a weightlifter like you,
I turned on and turned off the lights of the weightlifting training room. Why?
Because I didn't have the skill? Not at all!
The character as much as your inborn talent—
- What the professor's saying is to turn off the lights well, understand?- YES!
- Attention! Bow!- Goodbye!
Go! Dismiss!
Let's go.
Athlete Lee, what's today's meal menu?
Stir-fried spicy pork, bean sprout soup, beans cooked in soy sauce, stir-fried anchovy.
Ohh, stir-fried spicy pork! Be wanted!
- Metal cooking plates! - Be wanted!
Then let's go to the metal cooking plates for the first time in a long time.
Attention here. Stop.
Today, there is an event at the small gym.
- What?! - Again?
Seriously, why do we have to do this after every event? We aren't their slaves.
I mean, seriously. Are we the only muscles they can use?
In judo, shot-putting... rowing, too, the women players have thunder thighs. ( very wide thighs)
They probably won one hundred of the gold medals at the last National Sports Game.
- Let's give it our all! - Yes!
Indeed, we eagerly look forward to seeing the race he will do against the champion in the final.
The swimmers are getting ready to take their places.
According to the prelim results, lane 4 is assigned to Swimmer Jeong Joon Hyeong.
The left side, lane 5 is assigned to Swimmer Choi Tae Woon.
Yes, that's right. Even though it's done with the results of prelim,
from Swimmer Choi Tae Woon's standpoint, he can't get out of his nervousness about it.
The final heat is very interesting.
Yes, now they have taken their places.
The men's 200 meter...
Take your mark!
Ah! Swimmer Jeong Joon Hyeong in lane four had a false start.
Will he be disqualified again because of this?
Yes, that's right.
He'll get disqualified over this.
He got caught with the same false start as his last competition.
How disappointing for Swimmer Jeong Joon Hyeong.
Hey, Swimmer Jeong Joon Hyeong.
You know me, right? Choi Tae Woon.
I'm Choi Tae Woon's coach. Can we talk for a minute?
Aren't you already talking to me?
I have a favor to ask.
Could you be Tae Woon's personal training partner?
Be his personal training partner?
Our Tae Woon doesn't like training at Taerung.
So we're wondering if he should do some personal training.
I can enjoy training if I practice with someone in the similar level that's even a practice record.
It's good to give motivation to each other, kind of a win-win situation.
Ah, this is an honor.
When can a disqualified swimmer like me practice with a world-known swimming star like you?
But I sleep a lot in the early mornings, so it would be hard for me to do early morning training.
On the weekends, you have to rest.
Also, I'm picky about the water quality so we have to practice at my school pool.
Would you be able to adjust your practice to mine?
It won't do, right? It's fine, I thought so.
It's so heavy.
Aish, really.
Ah, so annoying!
Why do we have to do this all the time?
Until when...
- Ow. - It's not like they're paying us.
Come out, come out.
Come out.
Hey, you guys. We need to lay out the chairs, will you move?
Hey, are you deaf? I said move, so we can lay out the chairs.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey. Weightlifter.
Why are you disturbing someone in the middle of practice? Just lay out the chairs on this side first.
Yes.
They are going crazy.
Aigoo, how sad. They're so pitiful.
Who are you trying to pick a fight with?
Ahjumma, just lay out the chairs.
Did you see them laughing at us?
I am going to break those gymnasts' chopsticks!
Leave them alone. We have to be on the same physical level to have a proper conversation.
I knew it would happen.
Why did they bother us? I knew it.
How dare they to us?
Oh, sorry. Can you give me the ball?
Ah, sorry. I can't control my strength that well.
Ah, this is the last one. Ugh.
Ah, really.
- Bok Joo, are you okay? - Are you okay?
Can you stand up?
Look at her.
Those jerks.
Oh, human tsunami.
Get up.
I've already eaten but I'm still hungry!
- I should eat a sausage. - Hey, how many did you bring?
Give me one. Hey, Weightlifter Kim, cheer up already!
Just think like you stepped on dog poop (got bad luck).
Stepping on dog poop would be better! What an embarrassment.
Hey, should I just drop out? Or should I just stick my nose in a bowl of water and die?
Hey, hey, it's okay. Even if the rumors circulate today and tomorrow, they'll disappear soon.
I'll be generous. Eat this lovely sausage and cheer up.
Yeah. Cheer up Bok Joo. She's making this much of an effort.
Weightlifting Fairy Kim Bok Joo! Milky skin Kim Bok Joo!
Stop it.
Sausage.
Shall I have a sausage, since two of weightlifters are asking so earnestly?
Of course.
If many of us went there...
How many do you have?
Oh no!
Oh!
Omo, Weightlifter Kim!
Are you okay?
WHAT?
I thought I cut off a finger.
Are you all right?
I'm fine, but
I think my sausage just died.
You should've kept the proper speed in the school yard. Don't you know "keep eyes forward"?
Then do you want me to pray for the soul of the departed sausage?
What did you say "praying for"?
But have I seen you somewhere? You look familiar.
What?
I'm sure I've seen this face before...
That's because she participated in the National Games and the article about it came out on the bulletin board.
Anyhow, I apologize for this death but I also have a misfortune today, so...
Oh, excuse me, this may seem out of the blue in this situation,
but do you possibly like Messi? (Famous Argentine soccer player)
Pardon?
Never mind, it's a bit sudden, right?
Then, please be careful on your way.
Depart!
Okay! Alright! Be careful.
Aish, his way of talking is seriously annoying.
Maybe I should have gotten the price of the sausage out of him.
What's wrong? He's so fresh.
Don't you know him? He's the famous flower boy swimmer.
Flower boy, my ass. I'm sure it's "common," not "flower boy".
His face is just common.
But what did you say to him earlier? Something about Messi?
"Excuse me, but do you like Messi?"
It's my best tip.
Men are attracted to women who have the same common interests as them.
What do guys like the most?
Sports. Among sports, soccer!
He'll want to have a glass of alcohol with a woman who like Messi.
That seems possible. Doesn't that seem convincing?
You're really passionate about blabbering nonsense.
Don't talk back what you're saying.
Aish, what do you mean, what nonsense am I saying?  "Do you like Messi?"
Ah, why am I so unlucky today?
Oh, I think that jerk dropped this.
Oh, look at this preferences. Is he a pervert or what?
Were you nervous before the match? Your thigh is so tense.
It's not that, but I was a bit startled because of Sausage.
Sausage?
There's something like that.
Aren't you putting your personal feelings into this?
Hey, I'm sorry but I don't feel anything for you.
That can't be. With a thigh like this, your heart should flutter a bit.
Aigoo, please try to make my heart flutter.
All done. Just be careful for today. And massage it once more before going to bed.
I understand. Thank you.
What's wrong? Are you looking for something?
No, no.
If you guys don't know, who does?
We're telling the truth. We gave you everything we pulled out of the washing machine.
You don't know what I went through to get that when I was in Canada.
By any chance, couldn't this be the work of that big pig?
What?
The Weightlifting Club. Their washing machine breaks easily, so they use ours often.
They put on a big show because we left one piece of laundry before. They're doing it again just like last time!
Hey, Weightlifters!
Yes?
Come here.
You're first years right?
Yes.
You guys, did you see my tights?
Did they not get mixed in with your laundry when you used our washing machine?
No, it didn't.
How could I believe that?
Hey, what are you doing with our kids?
- Sunbaenim! - Sunbaenim!
What is it?
This unni's clothes went missing, and she's telling us to give them.
We really didn't use RG's washing machine because they complain so much these days.
Is that true?
Yeah. I did.
Do you have any evidence?
Do you think I would make this up?
I asked, do you have evidence that our kids took it?
I don't have evidence but you have the previous convictions.
Is it once or twice that you used our washing machine?
This is nothing to do with the previous convictions. You need to have evidence.
That's why our society hasn't improved. Ex-convicts can't start their life anew at ease.
Don't uselessly bother our kids, got it?
Let's go, kids.
- Sunbaenim, you're the best! - Sunbaenim, you're the best!
Right?
It looks delicious.
Yeah!
Now, they're even labeling us as laundry thieves.
They're making their eyes like this. If they gave a sidelong scowl a little bit more, their eyes would be on the back of their heads.
Are we jinxed with those chopsticks? I wonder why we've gotten tangled up with them in everything.
Hey, our dark history with them goes much further back than just yesterday and today.
This is all thanks to you. Let's keep this up and win.
Yes! Rhythmic Gymnastics Club
- Great job! - Wow!
-The RG Club's practice room they're using right now used to be our Weightlifting Club room.Weightlifting Club
Was it during the Asian Games? I heard that our seniors shed tears of blood after losing it to the RG Club who won Gold.
- Wow! - Noona, I love you!
Is that a puppy or a bear?
Is she wearing that shirt or did she draw it on?
Is that all?
Every single time we have a field day, we're always put right next to each other and get humiliated.
Still, that's nothing compared to the Goo Seul revolt last year.
Ah, Goo Seul revolt!
Soo Sang! Soo Sang, you can hear me, right?
If you want, I won't put any chalk on my hands anymore (I'll quit weightlifting). I'll only touch powder for my face!
Seriously, what's the problem?
- Is this a problem? Don't you see this? - No, you're fine!
What's wrong?!
It's you, isn't it? It is you.
Unni!
This bad wench! You just have a mouth hole but no flesh at all.
You don't have even any size!
Aigoo! Really!
Unni Goo Seul almost made a boyfriend after one year of effort,
but RG Club seduced him. Ugh!
In the end, that unni was kicked out of the dorms.
After that shock, she couldn't even remember well.
That's what I'm saying. To me, she was a very promising rhythmic gymnast.
Anyway, those RG people are aggravating. They don't give up anything at all.
Bok Joo, we're out of chicken.
Huh? Okay.
Ah! Uncle!
You should stop eating now. This is already your 4th chicken.
- It's our 3rd! - It's our 3rd!
I'm sorry. I committed a sin worthy of death.
Eat until your stomachs burst, Do, Mi, and Sol.
- Why hit us? - Why hit us?
Then at least pay before you eat!
Please leave immediately.
Is this a chicken grave?!
Hey, hey, hey! Bok Joo, we have 10 minutes before they take attendance! 10 minutes! Hurry up!
- Go, hurry! - Ah, oh my god!
Wow...
Why are you here? Isn't it almost time for night attendance?
Goodbye!
Yeah, yeah...
Ah Dad! I told you to make Hae Too do the delivery. I'll go to the hospital--
What is that? Dad, you picked that up on the street again, didn't you?
Someone threw this perfectly fine thing away. It was clean on the inside too.
They must have thrown it away because it can't make rice anymore! What are you going to use that for?
Why wouldn't I have a use for this, you rascal? I can put chicken in here for delivery
and that, what is that...
Even when you think about it, it doesn't make sense, right?
Hey, be quiet! Hurry up and leave!
Shove that chicken into your mouth with moderation!
Don't you have anything to do? Leave! Don't come tomorrow either!
Just throw that away, Dad. I'll see you at the hospital. Bye!
- Hurry! - Hurry up!
Hey, run slower! You'll get hurt!
Ugh! Those pretty kids.
Aigoo, run!
Come on!
Ugh, let's do some laundry.
Ah, I smell sweat.
What's wrong?
I just thought something was there.
What's there? Nothing's there.
Really?
Let's go.
We'll start taking attendance. Team Captain, please come to the head resident's room.
Hey, haven't you seen a handkerchief?
A handkerchief, my ass. Just clean up.
Hey, hurry up! Gi Seok will be here to check soon.
Ah, where could that have gone? Did I leave that at home?
Hey, hey, hey, hey! He's right next-door, next-door!
You two are in charge of the stairs, right?
Did you mop?
Of course, Sunbae.
You left alone in the middle of the competition.
My condition wasn't good.
What's to brag about being disqualified?
I told the coach before I left.
That's why I'm saying this. You don't think about your teammates or comrades, do you?
You only think about yourself, right?
After listening to your words, I think I was wrong.
After listening?
This bastard, seriously...
Team Captain, what are you doing? Do you want to spend the night here?
Yes, I'm coming!
Good work.
Ugh!
That sociopath, seriously! Every time he sees you, he can't wait to scold you.
I have a character that aggravates people.
Imagine if you were a senior. Would you adore a junior who does whatever he wants?
Aw, you even made an anti-fan. You amazing rascal.
Was I too perfect? Too perfect to be a human?
Such a perfect bastard got disqualified again? Again?!
You're even worse than me, who placed 5th place. Just go, go out and die.
Fine! I feel refreshed after hearing you curse me out!
This bastard.
Aish!
Hey, forget that. Let's go out.
Let's go play some games.
Night attendance is over. Where would we go, you crazy bastard?
Come on! This is amazing!
Oh, Min Kyung! It's been a while. I haven't seen you before.
Wow, cheers! Here, have a drink. Here.
Cheers! Woo!
You're the swimmer, aren't you?
Wow, your shoulders are amazing.
I saw you on Hye Jin's SNS (social media).
Um, could you please give me your number?
My mom took my phone away.
My grades dropped recently
and she thought that was because of women...
Goodbye.
Hey! Hey, where are you going?
Hey!
Joon Hyeong! You're going to eat, right? I'll set a place for you.
Of course! Just a minute, Mom!
Where the heck did you go?
Good morning.
Hey, you're out early.
Get in. I'll give you a ride.
Forget it. I'll just run there.
Just take the car. You must have had a hard time because of the competition.
Now you're talking about the competition?
Both Mom and Dad must have been so curious to ask, but neither of them said a word about the competition.
I guess acting cool is a genetic trait in our family.
Out of all of us, you're the most upset. There's no need for us to bring that up.
Yes, I deviated for the night because I was so upset
and since I can't be cool about it, I'll leave now.
I don't know if you'll be able to catch your younger brother with this crappy car.
What are you doing? Why aren't you following me?
Oh? Look at this.
Hey, Lee Seon Ok. You must be so excited, you gained 2 kilograms.
Um, I ate some chicken last night so...
Wow, you'll suffer big time right before the competition if you just eat whatever you want like this.
I told you this before, didn't I?
When the Olympics were held in Atlanta, in America,
when I had to change the weight class division suddenly and to reduce 3 kg in one week,
I starved myself, and at the sauna, I sweated out the rest of the pounds and barely made the needed weight.
And in any case, that's for someone like me, who looks after their body with extreme care. However--
- Hey! - Oh, that scared me.
You rascals, this is why we're telling you to take care of your body early on. Hold back on the meat.
- Yes! - Yes!
Aigoo, Trainer Yook!
- Oh? - Hello.
- Hello. - Kids, hello.
Hehe.
What brings you all the way here?
Someone ordered some chicken but cancelled their order and I couldn't think of anyone else to give it to.
Goodness, you don't have to do this. I have no words.
What are you talking about? You're making me upset.
Who's the one who created the Bok Joo of today?
She was tall and had long limbs
so she was wondering whether she should give up weightlifting, but you assured her that it was possible.
You told her that it was possible with her love for weightlifting. Do I have to list every single one of my thanks--
Applause!
- Thank you for the food! - We'll eat well.
- Thank you for the food! - Thank you!
Let's go.
Why did you come here? I would have gone to the hospital later.
You have to work some magic like this occasionally.
Do you know how much he looked after your comfort?
Ah, Professor Yoon! Eat with them, go eat!
I fried the middle size of chickens, not small ones.
Yes, I'll eat well.
Bok Joo. Since your father is here, you should escort him to the hospital.
Night practice is just individual practice anyway. Go on.
Thank you.
Hyung, Hyung! I think I have to leave for a bit.
Um, Jong Gi's father passed away.
You know him, my army comrade, right?
Of course, I know.
Huh?
But you know... Jong Gi's father
will be so happy you came in sparkly clothes.
What is it this time? A nighttime singer?
I'll go change.
Ugh, that lacking fool.
If he's going to put up an act, he should do it properly.
He only takes a role of the extra who doesn't speak one word all the time.
Okay, nice!
Your turn is good, Joon Hyeong. You're doing well.
Gi Seok, don't slack off.
Calluses.
Hey, hey, look. These are my scars of honor.
- You came, Weightlifter Kim? - You came?
Ah, why are you two always doing this in my room? The smell!
Even if you color your nails, the polish will just peel off if you weightlift.
I don't know why you slather it on.
It's not coloring, it's nail art.
Art, my ass. Just take off the calluses of your hands.
Don't cry after they come off all bloody when you're lifting barbells.
Hey, hey. Leave her alone. She has the same intention as " Do you like Messi?"
Hey, don't try to appeal to a man with these things but cultivate your inner side.
That's faster!
To be honest, we're much more charming than those RG kids.
We have good personalities, right?
We have amazing life skills, right?!
And we have this much glamor. Is there anything else to say?
- As expected, Kim Bok Joo's glamor is swag. - Swag.
Whenever I look at you, you're so positive. You have so much confidence.
You know, I don't know if that's confidence or bluff.
Nan Hee, out. Leave. Go to your own room!
Where did it go?
- Why? - What?
My cotton T-shirt I wore during my last competition, it's not here.
Where could that have gone?
Where did it go?
Really? You really don't know where my cotton T-shirt is?
Yes. I'm sure I saw it when I did the laundry.
Ah, this can't happen.
I wore that when I won gold in the last competition, so I have to wear it again for my next one.
It's not here, I can't find it.
It's not in our room and I asked all of the other rooms, but they don't have it either.
What will you do, Weightlifter Kim? You need to wear that for your competition.
Ah, I'm doomed. Without that shirt, I won't be able to win the medal either.
Um, by any chance, this is just a guess...
Isn't it possible the RG Club took it with the intent of getting revenge?
Ah, they said that we're the ones who took their clothes, so
on purpose they—
No... wait, Bok Joo! It was just a guess!
Hey, don't you know that she acts first and then thinks?!
Hey, Bok Joo!
I can just take a guess, can't I?!
What did we do to your clothes? We deliberately stole it?
- Did you not? - Are you crazy?
Why would we? What use would we have for that unfitting smelly rag?
You said that we were the ones who took your clothes
but you have no evidence, so out of anger—
We stole your clothes as revenge?
I'm about to go crazy.
- I guess she thinks we're as immature as they are. - I know.
Do you have evidence? You were the one who said evidence was the most important.
Yeah, so I'm going to look for some evidence.
Let me see your rooms for a minute.
No. Why do I have to show you my room? Why?
I have to find those clothes. Move.
What's wrong with you? Seriously, what are you doing?
Those are my lucky clothes. I have to find them.
I said no!
You'll get hurt, move!
- Ah, seriously! - Why are you like this?!
- Ah, I got it! - Move!
- Unni! - Unni!
Health Care Center
Who said you could relax now? Arms straight!
Bok Joo, get up.
What is this? Hey, are you a gangster?
Or like the other students say, are you a human bulldozer? Why would you hit someone with the strength you use to lift a barbell?
No, I was wrong.
Ah, is that the reason why you strengthen your upper body and exercise so much?
- But what happened today was— - Don't make excuses.
You've already caused the accident and excuses like that don't work anymore.
Behave properly. Hey, we're the club that uses our strength.
If you mess up, the entire club will be blamed. Understand?
Professor.
It seems her muscle was overused. She has to be careful for 2-3 weeks.
What you did was so unlike you, why?
I didn't do that on purpose, Coach.
She blocked me from entering her room so I just slightly pushed her and...
I'm telling the truth! I didn't use any strength.
Yeah, I know.
But you should still apologize. From now on, avoid contact with the RG Club as much as possible.
Ugh, seriously.
Goodness.
Hey, the professor apologized profusely to Coach Seong.
He's doing that in case problems arise in the future, so just do as he tells you.
I'm sorry.
What? I can't hear you at all.
I said I'm sorry! I'm sorry. Happy now?
I don't know. Ah,
I'll look at your behavior from now on and decide whether I'll forgive you or not.
Let's go.
Wow, those people are jerks.
I can't help it because I got so furious.
Come on.
Here you go. Yeah. ♬  How can I get your love  ♬
Let's drink here until drunk.
Cheers! ♬  How can I make you smile ♬
♬  This heart-throbbing excitement  ♬
Today was a really long day.  ♬ colors my feelings  ♬
What is all this drama over a single laundry machine?
Anyway, what are we going to do about your cotton T-shirt, Bok Joo? You said that was your lucky T-shirt.
Aish! RG, those jerks!
Our dad's words are right. "When you don't like food, you can give it to the dog but when you don't like a person..."
Hey, you rascals! Is having a pretty face and being popular everything?!
You have to become humane first.
She's right!
We both have smelly breath in the morning when we wake up!
Don't act up, you rascals!
Still, we are C-cup size and you're flat.
Even the expression of flat is too much for them.
Ugh, it's so loud! You're the weightlifting club, aren't you?!
No.
We're the Judo Team.
♬  I don't know where this feeling came from  ♬
Bok Joo, if both Song Joong Ki and Kim Soo Hyun asked you out at the same time, what would you do? ♬  There's a small quake only known to me  ♬
Can't I date both at the same time?
Hey, you wench! Have a conscience. You can't choose to eat both meat and sushi at the same time.
Hey, why can't I? I've lived my entire life being cautious of others and yielding.
I don't think this is something to fight over. Look up at the sky.
The weather is so nice.
Hey Jeong Nan Hee, where's the fish jerky we bought?
You all ate it all last time.
- Hey, I didn't eat that much! - I didn't eat it!
I really didn't eat it! You always blame me.
Aish, I'm so hungry.
You didn't say clearly in the end.
Fine, I ate it.
Go buy some more!
Ah, Joon Hyeong! Let's go out.
Let's go out!
Head resident went to bed and I checked Hyung Gi Seok also went to bed.
I don't want to. I'm tired today.
Just one hour. Let's just play some games for exactly one hour.
Friend...
It's not even two hours or three hours, but just one hour...
I just want to play games for just one hour, yet you just don't listen. You're making me upset!
- Goodness! I'm so upset, I feel so wronged! - Aish!
Ugh! You're bothering me so much, you bastard.
If you keep doing this, I might ask the teacher to give me a different room.
You're still going out now, right?
Yeah, let's go. Let's go, you bastard.
Joon Hyeong, I love you. Honey, I love you.
Don't do it.
Aish, get away.
Who's there?
What, who's there? Stop!
Just where did they go?
Did she leave?
She left, she left.
Pervert! Pervert!
Pervert! Catch him!
Hey, catch him! Pervert! Pervert!
Hey, where are you going!?
Hey! Come down.
What? What is that? Hey, hurry up and come down. Hurry up!
Hey, you perverted bastard!
Hey! He's here, he's here! I caught the pervert!
- I caught the pervert! - Let go of me!
Let go!
- Let go of me! Let go! - Where do you think you're going, you perverted bastard?!
- Hey, hey! Where do you think you're going?! - Let go of me! Hey!
- Hey! Hey! - Pervert!
- Hey, hey, hey! Aish! - Pervert!
- I caught him! - Hey!
I caught him!
I'm telling you it's not me.
It is him. I saw him clearly.
What are you talking about?
I just sneaked out to go to a PC room but then she suddenly appeared and...
I mean, if I like someone, I can just date them. Why would I steal female clothing?
That's why you're abnormal.
I clearly saw you. I have perfect eyesight.
- I'm about go nuts, seriously! - Um,
even if you saw him, there's no evidence that he's the pervert.
And to be honest, he's not the type to do that even though he jokes around a bit.
For now, let's settle this here.
Alright, well...
Hey, you rascal. Be prepared to receive demerit points.
Ah, but how did those people get past the security? I have to change it something else or something.
You can't just let him go! He's really a strange kid!
He even carries around a lace handkerchief, a girl's handkerchief.
What?
You perverted bastard.
Give me my handkerchief.
You should give me my cotton T-shirt.
Why are you asking me for your cotton T-shirt?
Then I can't give you your handkerchief either.
Fine, let's do this.
I warned you, didn't I?
I told you that you would be caught red-handed big time. You slimy bastard.
Do you know why I hate you so much?
Because you think you're so amazing.
I can see that conceitedness in your face, but don't misunderstand.
What's the use of breaking a record during training? You have a fragile mentality that always breaks whenever it's time for a competition.
People like you, who aren't terrible but aren't amazing, are the worst.
Know your place before you act up.
Make sure you jump 100 times, have a conscience.
Ugh, this is hard!
Joon Hyeong!
Joon Hyeong! Joon Hyeong! Joon Hyeong!
Hey, Joon Hyeong! I'm sorry, I was wrong! Joon Hyeong! Joon Hyeong!
Hey, get up.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Hey,
- Water. - Water? Water.
Alright, I got it. I'll get you premium luxurious foreign water... Wait, do I have some spare change?
Hey, I'll go...I'll go the fountain and get some change quickly—
You're terrible at everything!
Hey, Joon Hyeong! Joon Hyeong!
Ah, Hyungnim. Hyungnim, I'm sorry. Are you okay?
- I didn't mean to do that but— - Let go!
Joon Hyeong. Joon Hyeong, I-I was wrong.
Why are you doing this to me!?
I committed a sin worthy of death, Joon Hyeong!
Forget it. I'll go get the water myself.
Let's see, let's see.
Thank you. I will use this well.
You're a habitual thief.
I was wondering where all of the coins the students threw into the fountain disappeared to.
Don't throw them into the wishing fountain.
That's littering coins. Do you know how many coins are thrown away each year?
I'm doing all of this for the environment.
Is that so? You're such an amazing environmentalist.
Forget it. Give me back my handkerchief.
Me?
To you, Mr. Pervert? Why?
Hey, give it back while I'm being nice.
Hey, Sausage!
- Hwaiting! - Hwaiting!
Weightlifting! Fighting!
- Hwaiting!
Hey! Give me back my handkerchief!
Give me back my shirt first!
Joon Hyeong, don't you come here quickly?!
Female Dormitory
Death penalty.
That's not just a regular handkerchief. Give it back now.
My shirt isn't just a regular T-shirt either. It's special too.
Hey, you're going to be so sorry towards me in the future. What will you do? It'll be less difficult for you if you just give it up now.
I wish I could be sorry towards you.
2017 Rhythmic Gymnastics National Representative Audition
The next competitor will use a ribbon. Competitor 5, Song Si Ho.
2017 Rhythmic Gymnastics National Representative Audition, the first round.
A 3rd year at Haneol Sports College, this is Song Si Ho's ribbon performance.
The music selected is Ivan's Tango.
2017 Rhythmic Gymnastics National Representative Audition
What kind of school has so many events?!
Speaking of which, I have to find my lucky T-shirt.
Hey, you know that swimmer... Are you sure he's a pervert?
I mean, there's no way someone who looks like that would be a pervert.
Again, again! You concentrate too much on visuals, you wench. You can't be fooled by that face.
But even I think he's not like that.
Well, it's not as if I would frame him out of ill intentions.
Bicycle.
- Sausage. - Ah, seriously, what do you see me as?!
Ah, I don't know either!
The icon of thoughtlessness.
If you want to know about me, you have to go a long way. Hey, you go quickly!
- Ah, sorry! - Sunbae, quickly! Hurry, hurry!
Hurry up! Hurry!
- Move aside! - Ugh!
Hey, hey, hey! How can you place the chairs like this? You have to stack them up neatly in the corner over there.
Ah, you guys have no common sense.
Tell them to bring all the boys back!
Oh!
Excuse me...
What is it?
You saw?
- Ah, let go! - Let go!
- Hey, you pervert! Let go! - Pervert!
Stick it to your ear. That's right.
Raise up, and take off your hand. Get your balance. That a girl.
Nice job. Press down more.
Unni, you received your clothes, right? That old man is seriously sick.
I know. We didn't know and just framed the Weightlifting Club.
We both misunderstood each other so just pretend that nothing happened.
You two, don't yield to them just because you're sorry.
Oh, who's talking?! Concentrate on stretching your body!
Dani, press your heel down more. Continue.
Yi Seul, your heel is turning. Press down.Haneol Sports College
Coach, Si Ho Unni is here.
- Is he the one? - He stole female clothing?
- Old man, what are you looking at? Huh? - What is he staring at?
- Someone like him exists? - Ugh, pervert.
- How can there be someone like that? - What in the world?
- Perverted bastard - Ugh.
- He shouldn't do that. - Pervert.
Hey! Let's go! Hurry!
- In the future, you should tell sunbaes... - Ah, seriously...
I feel lost.
They always say that the darkest place is under the candlestick. You just never know by how they look.
Let's go.
Come on, Bok Joo.
Hey, what should we eat?
Hey, not that!
Why did that jerk jump in at that moment of all times and put me in this awkward situation...
What do I do...
I'm sorry, but can you open the door for me?
Thank you.
Are you in room 302 too?
Y-Y-Yes.
Nice to meet you. I'm Song Si Ho, a 3rd year at RG Club.
I'm going to share this room with you.
Only this room is available. I just came back from Taereung because I failed to make the cut for the national team.
I'm looking forward to staying with you well.
Hey,
isn't she Song Si Ho from the RG club?
She says she's my roommate...
It'll be tiring for you.
What can I do?
Excuse me, you said your name was Bok Joo, right? Could you close the window?
I have a weak bronchus so I can't catch a cold. Sorry about that.
I have a lot of body heat, so I leave it open though...
Excuse me. Also in your closet, could you make some space for me? There's no room.
Yes. Ah, I used to just use it alone, so...
Here you go.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by I'm Busy Getting Stronger Team @ Viki
Hey, hey, hey, Joon Hyeong! Did you hear the news? The Dorm Pervert was caught.
It was the jerk man who works in the administration office and looks very fishy. Now, you cleared yourself.
Why did that old man steal clothing?
I don't know. But rather, here's even more shocking news:
Song Si Ho came back from Taereung.
Your ex-girlfriend came back because she failed at the first round of the National Representative Audition.
Why did she do that?
Excuse me...
Excuse me?
You know, the guy that's tall, has a really sharp face,
and always rides a bike?
Who is she talking about?
I don't know.
That person the students always call handsome or whatever, that...
Are you looking for me?
Tall, sharp faced, and always rides a bike.
It's me, isn't it?
Excuse me, this.
I'm sorry for the misunderstanding. As an apology, I even washed it so—
Why did you wash this? Who told you to wash this however you wanted?!
Hey! Is it a sin to wash a handkerchief?! I felt sorry, so
I thought to myself that I should at least give this to you first. I'm even late for my practice, but I brought it anyway!
Wow! You're picking a fight over nothing. You have no manners.
- Give it back! I'll dirty it up again! Give it to me. - Let go.
I'll dirty it up again! Give it back!
Let go!
Hey!
♬  How can I get your love?  ♬
♬  How can I make you smile?  ♬
♬  This heart-throbbing excitement  ♬
♬  colors my feelings  ♬
♬  you and I in my dream  ♬
♬  I don't know where this feeling came from  ♬
♬  There's a small quake only known to me  ♬
Weightlifting Fairy Kim bok Joo Preview
Why are you acting impishly, not like you?
Why is this so fun?
Fatty! Give me a high five, give me a high five!
You little!
I guess we have some sort of fate.
Excuse me, teacher?
I just came back because I missed you.
It's been a while.
Excuse me, one moment.
Have we perhaps met each other before?
Train well. Don't get hurt.
Even if you talk like that, to be honest,
your heart is fluttering, isn't it?
It was nice seeing you! See you again soon, Fatty!